[Professional subtitles are being translated. Will be updated soon]
【专业字幕正在翻译中。很快就会更新]
for you
给你
Hello everyone, hello everyone.
大家好，大家好。
Completed
完成的
Arrived, arrived
到达了，到达了
today
今天
I will let everyone
我会让大家
little magic
小魔法
Draw with a group of bacteria
用一组细菌来画
here we go.
开始了。
This is a group of bacteria that I cultured.
这是我培养的一组细菌。
Let everyone take a look.
让大家看看吧。
Have you seen it?
你见过吗？
There is a little something.
有一点点东西。
Hundreds of thousands of people watching
数十万人观看
As a science newscaster
作为一名科学新闻播音员
You can use this process.
可以使用这个流程。
Magic wand
魔术棒
just like you
就像你这样
How much money can you make in a day?
一天能赚多少钱？
What changes next?
接下来会发生什么变化？
Live broadcast, take it with you
直播，随身携带
If you receive other ads
如果您收到其他广告
Tens of thousands a month is no problem.
一个月几万没问题。
This is easier than boiling it in the lab.
这比在实验室煮沸更容易。
Making money is much easier.
赚钱要容易得多。
Such a high income
这么高的收入
Why are you still stealing samples?
为什么还偷样品？
a while.
一会儿。
You will see magic.
你们会看到魔法的。
OK
好的
closed.
关了。
Let's see the results.
让我们看看结果。
I'm so excited.
我太激动了。
The magic is coming.
魔法来了。
Are you OK
你好吗
Amazing, right?
很神奇，对吧？
Admission notice has been announced.
录取通知已经公布。
Thank you for your concern.
谢谢大家的关心。
sorry.
对不起。
At this time, the paper cannot be published.
此时，论文还不能发表。
Please wait while I go to class.
请等我去上课。
Everyone is waiting patiently.
大家都在耐心等待。
OK
好的
That’s enough for today’s live broadcast.
今天的直播就够了。
Thank you all for coming.
谢谢大家的到来。
Good night, go to bed early.
晚安，早点休息吧。
After multiple layers of filtering
经过多层过滤
I saw her discomfort.
我看到了她的不适。
Don’t you plan to go to Australia to study?
你不打算去澳大利亚读书吗？
She published a paper.
她发表了一篇论文。
So what's so embarrassing about this?
那么这有什么尴尬的呢？
There is a problem with the paper.
论文有问题。
falsification science
证伪科学
possible
可能的
I think he is fake.
我觉得他很假。
Why?
为什么？
Did you see the comments just now?
大家看到刚才的评论了吗？
There is a passage that reads:
有一段这样写：
Her family conditions are very good.
她的家庭条件非常好。
but i remember
但我记得
Her family background is very ordinary.
她的家庭背景很普通。
She seemed to add another sentence
她似乎又补充了一句
Add another layer of filtering
添加另一层过滤
This live broadcast is not for everyone to see in vain.
这次直播没有白给大家看。
So, sir, please give me a reward.
那么，先生，请给我奖励吧。
The prize has been completed.
奖品已完结。
Thanks
谢谢
How is Huang Zicheng?
黄子成怎么样了？
Bangkok
曼谷
Get on with his game.
继续他的比赛。
you change the sample
你改变样本
This isn't just about freeing up long queues.
这不仅仅是为了释放长队。
If Han Jie is captured
如果韩洁被俘
Ye Wu must know.
夜雾肯定知道。
We have intervened.
我们已经介入了。
Huang Zicheng’s situation
黄子成的情况
This is very dangerous.
这是非常危险的。
Yes
是的
But Huang Zicheng
但黄子成
This is a very good breaking point for us.
这对我们来说是一个非常好的突破点。
We have a responsibility.
我们有责任。
keep him safe
保护他的安全
But now his situation is not good.
但现在他的处境并不好。
do you know?
你知道吗？
Why did Ye Wu drag him into the water?
夜雾为何把他拖入水中？
affim
肯定
Likewise, he
同样，他
Its value lies in its usefulness.
它的价值在于有用。
use him
利用他
espionage target
间谍行动的目标
Yes
是的
so you
那么你
Gradually
逐步地
Drag him into the water?
拉他下水？
I just hope Yewu still wants to take advantage of him.
只希望夜雾还想利用他。
Wouldn't hurt him easily.
不会轻易伤害他。
What I'm afraid of now is
现在我害怕的是
I don't give up that easily.
我没那么容易放弃。
The more you resist, the more dangerous you are.
越是反抗，就越危险。
boss
老板
Today's order
今天的订单
OK
好的
Han Jie received a message.
韩杰收到一条消息。
What?
什么？
Product box number 13
产品盒号13
The suspect will then deliver the product.
然后嫌疑人将交付产品。
The target is operational.
目标已开始运作。
Come on, come on, it's them.
来来来，就是他们。
Come on, come in.
来来来，进来吧。
Are you OK? Any questions?
你好吗？有什么问题吗？
Thirteen boxes, right?
十三盒吧？
Yes, 13 boxes.
是的，13个箱子。
You carry these first, you transport these first.
你先携带这些，你先运输这些。
Those are me.
那些是我。
able
能
OK, wait a minute.
好，等一下。
Lock the door.
把门锁好。
Well, trust me.
好吧，相信我。
You push the car back first.
你先把车推回去。
follow him
跟着他
The temperature inside the locomotive is low.
机车内温度较低。
You only have 15 minutes.
你只有 15 分钟的时间。
I'll take you out after this.
在此之后我会带你出去。
Be careful.
当心。
I see.
我明白。
I found it
我找到了
open for business
开始营业
surpass him
超越他
Have you received the goods?
您收到货了吗？
knew.
知道了。
put it
把它
The car has arrived, let's go.
车已经到了，走吧。
admit
承认
release
发布
sorry Sorry.
对不起，对不起。
There was a minor accident.
发生了一起小事故。
minor accident
小事故
You were almost frozen into an ice sculpture.
你几乎被冻成了冰雕。
you can not
你不能
Can I please come in advance?
可以请提前吗？
have
有
This is it.
就是这个。
I told you in advance
我提前告诉过你
You lift this up.
你把这个举起来。
Then you won't do it?
那你不做吗？
Come on, hold me.
来，抱住。
God
上帝
Come on, come on, put on another one.
来来来，再穿上一件。
Post another one.
再贴一张。
Come on, come on, carry it on your back.
来来来，背在背上。
Are you ok?
还好吗？
Can you turn on the heating for me?
你能帮我打开暖气吗？
Come on, turn up the heat.
快来把暖气打开吧。
OK
好的
The target has entered customs.
目标已进入海关。
I see.
我明白。
Thanks
谢谢
Researcher evaluation completed
研究人员评价完成
The following example B13
后面的示例 B13
real
真的
Not too bad.
不算太差。
normal practice
正常练习
Used to transport seafood for protection.
用于运输海鲜以起到保护作用。
This could be Jin Hae's spy.
这可能是金海的间谍。
in gimhae
在金海
I sent someone to monitor Han Jie.
我派人去监视韩洁。
Hope to find some clues.
希望能找到一些线索。
from himself
来自他自己
Yes
是的
Change this example to the cleaning lady
改变这个例子的清洁女工
Until now, we haven't found it.
直到现在，我们还没有找到。
Do you have any clues?
你有什么线索吗？
That person is familiar with the institute.
那个人对研究所很熟悉。
very familiar
很熟悉
With Yu Xiaoyue
与余小月
perfect cooperation
完美合作
You suspect that he knows Yu Xiaoyue.
你怀疑他认识于小月。
Maybe this is the person we're looking for.
也许这就是我们要找的人。
So professor
所以教授
Director Qin
秦主任
I recommend it to Xiaoyue
我推荐给小悦
secret search
秘密搜查
confirm her identity
确认她的身份
agree
同意
I've been eating these for years.
我已经吃这些东西很多年了。
Aren't you greasy?
你不油腻吗？
That's very good.
那挺好的。
Sometimes you have to change the taste.
有时你必须改变口味。
I don't like taking risks.
我不喜欢冒险。
i see you at work
我看到你在工作
This is equally dangerous.
这同样危险。
So that's enough.
所以这就足够了。
when you work
当你工作时
very funny
很有趣
able
能
So let's talk about special missions.
那么我们来谈谈特殊任务。
Say it.
说吧。
You said this game
你说这个游戏
What exactly is charm?
到底什么是魅力呢？
able to attract so many players.
能够吸引这么多玩家。
you need to know
你要知道
Why does Huang Zicheng have to play?
为什么黄子成一定要上场？
this game
这个游戏
this case
这个案例
It happened because of this game
因为这个游戏而发生
Then I must understand.
那么我必须明白。
I understand enough.
我足够理解了。
Then you go try it and see for yourself.
然后你就去尝试一下，亲眼看看。
Be reasonable
讲道理
Welcome to the spy game.
欢迎来到间谍游戏。
You must pass the interview.
您必须通过面试。
Get in-game features
获取游戏中的功能
During the interview
采访过程中
All questions must be answered honestly.
所有问题都必须诚实回答。
What's the name?
是什么名字？
Huang Zicheng
黄子成
Passport number
护照号
ED1910726
ED1910726
Profession
职业
Unemployed
失业的
Please wait
请稍候
Are you OK
你好吗
Didn't go in
没进去
I use my brother's name.
我用我哥哥的名字。
and registered passport information
和登记的护照信息
Already rejected me
已经拒绝我了
affim
肯定
This machine can distinguish
本机可以区分
photo of your face
你的脸的照片
and the identity information you provide
以及您提供的身份信息
inconsistent
不一致
So I can't get in
所以进不去
Why is real-name authentication still needed?
为什么还需要实名认证？
But even if you use your own name
但即使你用自己的名字
Not sure I can get in.
不确定我能不能进去。
Why?
为什么？
because of your career
因为你的职业
not disclose information
不透露信息
We are a confidentiality mechanism.
我们是一个保密机制。
Can't find it online
在网上找不到
Our careers information
我们的职业信息
Unless you say you're unemployed.
除非你说你失业了。
otherwise
否则
It will admit that you lied.
它会承认你撒谎了。
But unemployed
但失业了
Failed to pass inspection
无法通过检验
The game has thresholds.
游戏有门槛。
So it's just a game.
所以这只是一场比赛。
You can come and see us.
你可以来看看我们。
Is it that clean?
有这么干净吗？
What about the era of big data?
大数据时代又如何呢？
The traces you leave on the Internet
你在互联网上留下的痕迹
will be recorded
都会被记录下来
The game will pass.
比赛就会过去。
Facial and passport data recognition
面部和护照数据识别
Check everyone
检查大家
What needs to be clear is
需要明确的是
Come this far
走到这一步了
He must have
他一定有
Excellent technical team
优秀的技术团队
support behind
背后支持
not just ordinary people
不仅仅是普通人
Any game developer can do it.
游戏商都可以做。
That's what this game is.
这就是这个游戏。
The first attractive point
第一个吸引人的点
The real feeling is very strong.
真实的感觉非常强烈。
the second?
第二个？
High return
高回报
In-game transactions
游戏内交易
Can be redeemed
可以兑换
real money
真币
also
此外
There are also high prizes.
还有高额奖品。
Best Officer Competition
最佳军官比赛
this will attract
这会吸引
More professional players
更多职业选手
Use games to live
用游戏来生活
Yes
是的
The third?
第三个？
have no idea
不知道
People who can choose this game
可以选择这款游戏的人
They are all such people
他们都是这样的人
full of doubts
充满疑问
They want to use games to investigate.
他们想用游戏来调查。
this unknown world
这个未知的世界
The missions of both parties are unclear
双方的使命不明确
Full of unknown challenges
充满未知的挑战
Didn't realize it.
没有意识到。
Give it to someone who boasts.
把它送给一个自夸的人。
full of dangerous spirit
充满了危险的精神
The more I remember this game
我越记得这个游戏了
not understand
不明白
Arrived, arrived
到达了，到达了
Is it interesting?
它有趣吗？
Is not fun
不好玩
I want to help you.
我想帮助你。
Didn't he enter the officer status in advance?
不是提前进入军官状态了吗？
This is already too fast.
这已经太快了。
What time is it now, brother?
现在几点了，大哥？
You look at your phone.
你看看你的手机。
you think
您认为
Are we really on vacation?
我们真的在度假吗？
This place is probably
这个地方大概是
Delivery location
送货地点
Shipped so soon?
这么快就发货了？
This game is really boring.
这个游戏真的很无聊。
Spies spend their lives protecting secrets.
间谍一生都在保护秘密。
What does it mean?
意味着什么？
protect secrets
保护秘密
Still have to live
还是得活着
Play big
玩的很大
Yes
是的
Where is our secret?
我们的秘密呢？
Why are you here?
你怎么在这里？
I'm running errands.
我正在办事。
You can trust me.
你可以相信我。
Is this your first time in Thailand?
这是您第一次来泰国吗？
First time with a woman
第一次和女人在一起
you?
你？
I
我
I've been here before.
我以前来过这里。
alone
独自的
An iced Americano
一杯冰美式咖啡
Same, thank you.
一样，谢谢。
There seems to be someone behind.
后面好像有人。
Always follow us
一直关注我们
Don't look, don't look
别看 别看
Coffee is done.
咖啡完成了。
WHO？
WHO？
Maybe someone in this game.
也许是这个游戏中的某个人。
game
游戏
sorry Sorry.
对不起，对不起。
no problem, no problem.
没关系，没关系。
Have you been following us?
你一直在关注我们吗？
The trade is temporarily halted when a thief appears.
偷窃者出现 交易暂时停止。
What about insulated glass?
那么隔热玻璃呢？
It's open now
现在开门了
I already told you.
我已经告诉过你了。
This game is not that easy.
这个游戏并不那么容易。
It really doesn't exist anymore.
它真的不存在了。
No need to chase anymore.
没必要再追了。
She also had an accomplice.
她还有一个同伙。
We left through the back of the kitchen.
我们从厨房后面离开。
What does it mean?
意味着什么？
In fact, you are already prepared.
其实你已经做好了准备。
Why didn't you tell me in the first place?
为什么一开始就不告诉我？
Life is like a drama, it depends on acting skills
人生就像一场戏剧 靠的是演技
Are you OK?
你好吗？
not on computer
不在电脑上
in computer
在电脑里
Anything else?
还有别的事吗？
but
但
It appears to have been installed.
看来已经安装了。
CCTV software
闭路电视软件
Who's in the CCTV cameras?
闭路电视摄像机里有谁？
The other party has already cut it.
对方已经砍了。
never
决不
Search for deals online
在线搜索优惠
Do you want your passport back?
你想拿回你的护照吗？
Yes
是的
The experiment is over.
实验结束了。
I've already asked for leave.
我已经请假了。
I want my passport back.
我想要回我的护照。
cannot
不能
your situation
你的情况
Your passport has not been handed to you yet.
你的护照还没有交给你。
Why?
为什么？
This has not yet passed the confidentiality period.
这还没有过了保密期。
laboratory staff
实验室工作人员
Still unable to leave the country temporarily
仍暂时无法出境
But the experiment is complete.
但实验已经完成了。
No matter what your experiment is
无论你的实验是什么
When will it be completed?
什么时候能完成？
follow the rules
按照规则
There must be a two-month confidentiality period.
必须有两个月的保密期。
two months
两个月
I took it
我拿了
Can my passport be returned?
我的护照可以退回吗？
I remember it was about to expire.
我记得快要过期了。
I took it and changed it a little bit.
我拿了它并稍微改变了它。
no matter what difficulties you face
无论你面临什么困难
Can't break the rules
不能违反规则
This is because
这是因为
Is this the reason?
是这个原因吗？
Yes
是的
Why is it even a holiday?
为什么它甚至是假期？
I can't take it anymore.
我再也受不了了。
This is not a holiday.
这不是假期。
There is no need to go abroad.
没必要出国。
but
但
I don’t just go on vacation.
我不只是去度假。
I still have to participate.
我还得参加。
my relative's wedding
我亲戚的婚礼
I beg you to let me go.
我求你放我走。
able?
能？
relatively
相对的
Do you have relatives abroad?
你在国外有亲戚吗？
No
不
cousin
表哥
Then you should apply in advance.
那么你应该提前申请。
Now is a special time.
现在是一个特殊的时期。
I really can't approve it for you.
我实在无法替你批准。
I hope you can understand.
我希望你明白。
OK
好的
on her computer
在她的电脑上
When contacting online
在线联系时
We'll find out soon.
我们马上就会知道。
let's go.
我们走吧。
sir ray
雷爵士
come here.
你过来。
Dr. Byrne
拜恩博士
close the door
关门
I've seen your topic report.
我看过你的主题报告。
Well written
写得很好
That is, there are two points.
也就是说，有两点。
You can change it a little bit.
你可以稍微改变一下。
I get it, thanks Borders.
我明白了，谢谢边界。
That is,
那是，
Xiao Yu
萧宇
What's going on with you these days?
这些天你怎么了？
i see your condition
我看到你的状况
not too good
不太好
What's wrong?
有什么不对？
She hasn't been feeling well lately.
她最近身体不太舒服。
Maybe it's because I've done OT before.
也许是因为我之前做过OT。
I'm tired.
我累了。
like this
像这样
Please trust me. it's not a big deal.
请相信我。没什么大不了的。
able
能
you go.
你去。
So I'm leaving.
所以我要走了。
Yu Xiaoyue's home
于小月家里
No gaming equipment
没有游戏设备
phone computer
电话 电脑
There are no gaming apps either.
也没有游戏应用程序。
She may not be a professor.
她可能不是教授。
But she went to the library.
但她去了图书馆。
They also stole samples.
他们还偷走了样品。
she may be
她可能是
professor's subordinate
教授的下属
But her computer was monitored by CCTV.
但她的电脑被闭路电视监控到了。
Who is right?
谁是对的？
can't find it
找不到它
This is Yu Xiaoyue
这个于小月
Why do you have to work for a spy?
为什么你必须为间谍工作？
There is only one possibility.
只有一种可能。
She has been controlled by the professor.
她已经被教授控制了。
Samples have been sent.
样品已发出。
no surprise
没有意外
Your guys are doing pretty well.
你的人做得还不错。
Yu Xiaoyue's current condition is not very good.
玉小月现在的状态不太好。
What's wrong?
怎么了？
She was already panicking.
她已经惊慌失措了。
Today she went to the secret store.
今天她去了秘密商店。
Bring your passport.
带上你的护照。
I'm worried she'll be in trouble.
我担心她会有麻烦。
stupid
愚蠢的
I still think she is someone who can be used.
还是觉得她是一个可以利用的人。
She is not as innocent as she appears.
她并不像表面上表现的那么无辜。
You keep an eye on her.
你留意她。
If danger is found
如果发现危险
throw away immediately
立即扔掉
I know
我知道
Any news there?
那里有什么消息吗？
No
没有
real
真的
A little abnormal
有点不正常
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
There is no use overthinking.
想太多是没有用的。
The future is unpredictable.
未来是不可预测的。
If you see this action, stop the action.
如果你看到这个动作，就停止这个动作。
that's right.
这是正确的。
I really can't think of it.
我实在想不出来。
This offline mission is very exciting.
这次线下任务非常精彩。
Definitely already
肯定已经
Rewards are hard earned.
奖励来之不易。
this game
这个游戏
If only there were bonuses
如果只有奖金的话
Game level design
游戏关卡设计
if you are really stupid
如果你真的很傻
I do not want to play.
我不想玩了。
crazy
疯狂的
Don't you feel it?
你没感觉到吗？
Game experience and game rewards
游戏体验和游戏奖励
This is also important.
这也很重要。
Think about it.
你想想吧。
before playing games
在玩游戏之前
when you play games
当你玩游戏的时候
that adrenaline
那种肾上腺素
increased feeling
增加的感觉
after you win the game
当你赢得比赛后
that sense of honor
那种荣誉感
Yes, money can buy it, right?
是的，钱可以买到，对吗？
I can't figure it out at all.
我根本想不出来。
You are also passionate about games.
你也对游戏充满热情。
I used to be a professional gamer.
我曾经是一名职业选手。
Prizes and game steps
奖品及游戏步骤
as important as me
像我一样重要
Pros
职业选手
I've competed before.
我以前参加过比赛。
Still can't play?
还是玩不了？
How else would you get in?
不然怎么进去？
What about the secret mission we agreed on?
说好的秘密任务呢？
Not yet, not yet, because
还没有，还没有，因为
my old teammates
我的老队友
Always pulling me to play
总是拉着我玩
You have always been my partner.
你一直是我的伙伴。
Higher level than me
等级比我高
But this offline mission
不过这个线下任务
choose me
选择我
She wasn't chosen.
她没有被选中。
This made her angry.
这让她很生气。
partner
伙伴
Is it a woman?
是女人吗？
how do you know?
你怎么知道？
Honey
亲爱的
Tiezi
铁子
if you talk like this
如果你这样说话
My sister will be very sad.
姐姐会很难过的。
So between men and women
所以男人和女人之间
There is no real friendship.
没有真正的友谊。
small
小的
So we two are partners, right?
所以我们两个是搭档吧？
We are two different people.
我们两个人不一样。
Why are they different?
他们怎么不一样呢？
go.
去。
Sent a message but no reply.
发了消息但没有回复。
where are you going?
你要去哪里？
I can't wait for next year.
我等不及明年了。
I gotta go
我要走了
I will go abroad
我会出国
Why so suddenly?
为什么这么突然？
Isn’t the announcement for next year?
公告不是明年的吗？
There is no need to leave now.
现在没必要走。
Yu Xiaoyue
于小月
Apply to study abroad
申请出国留学
she may
她可能
use this opportunity
借此机会
He has fled abroad.
他已经逃到国外了。
I've told you the secret.
我已经告诉你这个秘密了。
can't let you go
不能让你走
Isn't it good to stay in the institute?
留在研究所不好吗？
We study this area.
我们研究这个领域。
two years ago
两年前
very developed
非常发达
And one more thing
还有一件事
List of Dr. Byun’s research group
Byun博士课题组名单
It's not easy to get.
想要得到并不容易。
I know you are the one who can help me.
我知道你是那个能帮助我的人。
come to me
到我这里来
You don’t have to stress this all the time.
你不必一直强调这一点。
I did not mean that.
我不是那个意思。
So what do you mean?
所以你是什么意思？
Reinforce it over and over again.
一遍又一遍地强调它。
You were the one who helped me get into the lab.
你是帮助我进入实验室的人。
I know
我知道
I know you helped me, Chu Lei.
我知道你帮了我，楚雷。
You help me with this, help me with that.
你帮我这个 帮帮我那个。
I know everything
我都知道
Can I thank you?
我可以谢谢你吗？
The relationship between the two of them
他们两个人的关系
It looks complicated.
看起来很复杂。
Give me Chu Lei's information again.
把楚雷的资料再给我一下。
This Shi Lei
这个石磊
He is Yu Xiaoyue's senior.
他是于小月的前辈。
The study has been accredited by the school.
该研究已获得学校认证。
after graduation
毕业以后
I was hired immediately.
我立刻就被录用了。
Research institute
研究机构
I have been following Dr. Byun ever since.
后来我就一直跟着Byun博士。
But he takes no responsibility.
但他不承担责任。
B13 project
B13项目
if you can help me
如果你能帮助我
thank you
我谢谢你
if you can't help me
如果你不能帮助我
Don't cause trouble for me here.
别在这里给我找麻烦。
What else do you want me to do for you?
你还想让我为你做什么？
My passport is confidential.
我的护照是保密的。
Can you think of a way?
你能想个办法吗？
Can you bring it to me?
你能把它带给我吗？
you are delusional
你有妄想症
what can I do?
我能做些什么？
Do I want to steal it for you?
我要给你偷吗？
OK
好的
Then let's break up.
那么我们分手吧。
What follows is my story.
接下来是我的故事。
You don't have to worry anymore.
您不必再担心了。
Yu Xiaoyue
于小月
You are with me.
你和我在一起。
Are you trying to take advantage of me?
这是要利用我吗？
Yes
是的
I don't need you now.
现在我不需要你了。
you go.
你去。
go.
去。
Chu Lei came out.
楚雷出来了。
Yu Xiaoyue called.
于小月打来电话。
Hello
你好
Yu Xiaoyue
于小月
This is me.
这就是我。
You come alone
你一个人来
I sent you the address.
我把地址发给你了。
I know, trust me.
我知道，相信我。
Are you going to meet the professor?
你要去见教授吗？
Probably
很有可能